Enthusiastic web development learner with about 1.5-year of experience in the broadly understood field of IT. Orientated for process automation and optimization. With high understanding of the importance of programming and UX for today's business.

# **Work History**

2023-01 - present **Junior Web Developer** 

AutoCare S.A

- · Code new fronted layout
- Code a little additional logic in Django

2019-01

- present

**Owner** 

Economics & Finance Expert Jakub Wojtysiak

- Financial Services
- Team Management
- Process Otimization

## **Education**

2016-10 - 2019-06

**Economics - Foreign Markets, Bachelor** 

Akademia Leona Koźmiskiego, Warszawa

2019-10 - 2021-06

Management & Logistics, Master

Akademia Leona Koźmiskiego, Warszawa

# **Projects**

2023-02 - present Automated Dialer (Android App) + Web Service

Technologies: SCSS, React, React Native, Firebase, Java

- Android app that makes automated calls based on previously uploaded XLS file. There was need to create own native module in Java to make directed calls
- · Firebase as a login and storage system
- Uploading and data display via connected Web Service

2023-02

- 2023-02

**Scandiweb Assignment Test** 

Technologies: SCSS, React, PHP, MySql, Apache

• Simple application that manages add/delete products with backend saving and data validation.

2023-02

FakeFlix (Netflix Clone)

Technologies: React, TMDB API

- Simple Netflix clone coded 100% by my self in order to learn React.
- · Features:
  - Search
  - Favourites
  - Randomly Generated Data
  - Preview

2022-10

- present

**Small Projects & Courses** 

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

# Jakub Wojtysiak

Web Developer



## **Personal Info**

#### **Email**

it.jakub.wojtysiak@gmail.com

#### **Phone**

+48 501 721 417

#### **Github**

@CodastickFantastic

### **Skills**

Fast learning skill Independance Self-discipline

# **Technologies**

HTML 5

CSS, SCSS

JavaScript, React, React Native

MySql, Firebase, Rest API

PHP(Basic), Python(Basic)

Figma, Addobe Photoshop & Xd

Windows, Linux

**Basic Cybersecurity** 

Basics of Networking and DNS

# Languages

English - B2

## Hobby, Interest

Illusion

**Technology** 

Markets

Self-development